Guide to the National Lawyers Guild Records TAM.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 1, Series XIV: Subject Files, 1936-1976
  - Smith Act, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Smith Act, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Social Legislation Post War, 1944-1950 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Social Legislation, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Social Legislation, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Social Legislation, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Social Legislation, 1950-1954 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Social Legislation: Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Social Legislation: Clippings, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Social Legislation: Medicare, Pensions, 1952-1960 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Social Security: Bills and Clippings, 1953-1955 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Social Security Brochure, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Social Security Coverage, 1962-1963 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Social Security for Lawyers, 1952-1955 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Social Security for Lawyers, 1954-1956 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Social Security for Lawyers [I], 1954 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Social Security for Lawyers [II], 1954 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Social Security for Lawyers, 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Social Security for Lawyers, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Social Security for Lawyers [I], 1956 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Social Security for Lawyers [II], 1956 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Social Security Requests for Pamphlets, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - SOHYO News: Journal from General Council of Trade Unions Japan, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Soldiers Vote, 1943-1944 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Southern Lawyers Defense Fund, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Speaker Ban, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Speaker Bureau, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Speaker Outline: "War in Vietnam", 1967 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Speeches/Addresses, 1937, 1945, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Staff Meetings: Notes, Memos, etc., 1954 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Staff Positions, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - State Bar Admission Rules: Various [I], Undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - State Bar Admission Rules: Various [II], Undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - State Bar Statement: California, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - State Department, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Statement of Policy and Program, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Stationery Information, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Students, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Students Affairs: Student Discussion, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Student Clerkships, 1961-1963 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Student Employment Program: California, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Students for a Democratic Society Convention, Jun 1967 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Supreme Court Decisions: Civil Rights, 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Supreme Court Opinions, Newspapers Clip, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Survey of Criminal Prosecutions in Massachusetts, 1949-1952 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Taxation [I], 1941, 1950-1959 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Taxation [II], 1941, 1950-1959 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Taxation, 1943-1944 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Taxation, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Tax Forms: Withholding and Social Security, 1944-1947 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Tax Tips, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Teachers Union, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Temporary Commission on the Courts, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Temporary Employees, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Theatre Party: "The Matchmaker", 1955 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Tokyo Rose, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Treasurer [I], 1951-1955 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Treasurer [II], 1953-1955 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - UE Committee on Un-American Activities, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Un-American Activities, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Un-Americans by Frank Donner, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - UN Committee on the Draft Convention on Freedom of Information, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Unemployment: Clippings, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1952-1959 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1954-1959 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - United Nations, Undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - United Nations, 1945-1953 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - United Nations Missions, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - United Tenants, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Universal Military Training, 1948, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Vets for Peace, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam and the Draft, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - War Criminals, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - War Resistance, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Washington DC Draft Conference, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Washington March, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Veterans' Affairs, 1944, 1948 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Rights Organization, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Wilke Memorial Building, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Wiretapping Bills, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Wiretapping: Bills, Clippings, Non-Guild Pamphlets, 1935-1955 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Wiretapping and Guild Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - World Peace Through Law, 1958-1961 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - World War II: Second Front, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Younger Lawyers, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Young Lawyers Round Table, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Your Rights in Selective Service, Undated (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Zajicek, Oldrich: Pamphlets, Publications, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Zucker, Helene R., 1949 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- Part 1, Series XV: Addendum, 1937-1968
  - Sub-Series A: Correspondence.
    - Correspondence between Chapters and National Office, 1948-1965 (Box 56a, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1947-1960 (Box 56a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series B: National Office Subject Files.
    - Administrative Law Committee, Undated (Box 56a, Folder 3)
    - Alder, et al v. Wilson, 1952 (Box 56a, Folder 4)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1953 (Box 56a, Folder 5)
    - Bar Associations, 1945-1963 (Box 56a, Folder 6)
    - Cancelled Memberships, 1947-1960 (Box 56a, Folder 7)
    - Capital District Chapter, 1949 (Box 56a, Folder 8)
    - Caughlan, John, 1954-1963 (Box 56a, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Chapter, 1951-1960 (Box 56a, Folder 10)
    - Citizens United for a Fair Housing Law in Rhode Island, 1961-1962 (Box 56a, Folder 11)
    - Civil Liberties Docket, 1955-1960 (Box 56a, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights Congress, 1949 (Box 56a, Folder 13)
    - Committee to Assist Southern Lawyers, 1962-1963 (Box 56a, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Civil Rights, 1947-1953 (Box 56a, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Immigration and Naturalization, 1949-1959 (Box 56a, Folder 16)
    - Committee on International Relations, 1942-1943 (Box 56a, Folder 17)
    - Committee for Legal Assistance in the South, 1962-1964 (Box 56a, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Post War Planning, 1945 (Box 56a, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Social Legislation, 1961-1967 (Box 56a, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Taxation, 1945 (Box 56a, Folder 21)
    - Constitution, 1951 (Box 56a, Folder 22)
    - Constitutional Civil Liberties Committee, 1961 (Box 56a, Folder 23)
    - Constitutional Rights and Liberties Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 56a, Folder 24)
    - Criminal Law Committee, 1948-1963 (Box 56a, Folder 25)
    - Davidson, Jessica, 1955 (Box 56a, Folder 26)
    - Disciplinary Proceedings Affecting the Independence of the Bar, 1948-1955 (Box 56a, Folder 27)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine, 1967-1968 (Box 56a, Folder 28)
    - Draft Counseling, 1948-1968 (Box 56a, Folder 29)
    - Editorial Board, 1948-1962 (Box 56a, Folder 30)
    - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 56a, Folder 31)
    - Emerson, Thomas, 1950-1954 (Box 56a, Folder 32)
    - Executive Board, 1947-1967 (Box 56a, Folder 33)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1949-1963 (Box 56a, Folder 34)
    - Feinberg Law, 1953 (Box 56a, Folder 35)
    - Finances, 1954-1956 (Box 56a, Folder 36)
    - Financial Statements, 1954-1963 (Box 56a, Folder 37)
    - France, Royal, 1956-1959 (Box 56a, Folder 38)
    - Fundraisers, 1953 (Box 56a, Folder 39)
    - Goodman, Crockett, Eden, Robb, and Philo Law Offices, 1963-1966 (Box 56b, Folder 1)
    - Guild Lawyer, 1945-1967 (Box 56b, Folder 2)
    - Income Survey, 1944-1949 (Box 56b, Folder 3)
    - Independence of the Bar Committee, 1955-1961 (Box 56b, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Judicial Administration, 1953 (Box 56b, Folder 5)
    - Intake, 1951-1967 (Box 56b, Folder 6)
    - Integration Committee, 1963 (Box 56b, Folder 7)
    - International Law Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 56b, Folder 8a)
    - International Law Committee (includes letter from Eleanor Roosevelt), 1947, 1960-1967 (Box 56b, Folder 8b)
    - International Law Committee: Palestine, 1946-1947 (Box 56b, Folder 8c)
    - International Association of Democratic Lawyers, 1955 (Box 56b, Folder 9)
    - Joint Committee on Administration, 1957-1958 (Box 56b, Folder 10)
    - Jordan v. Hutcheson, 1961-1962 (Box 56b, Folder 11)
    - Kenny, Robert, 1944-1947 (Box 56b, Folder 12)
    - Labor Law Committee, 1939-1959 (Box 56b, Folder 13)
    - Lawyers Committee for Justice in Palestine, 1951 (Box 56b, Folder 14)
    - Legal Education Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 56b, Folder 15)
    - Legal Papers, Undated, 1952-1965 (Box 56b, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles and Hollywood: Beverly Hills Chapters, 1953-1963 (Box 56b, Folder 17)
    - Loyalty Oaths, 1948-1956 (Box 56b, Folder 18)
    - Membership, 1937-1960 (Box 56b, Folder 19)
    - Michigan Chapters, 1959-1967 (Box 56b, Folder 20)
    - National Convention, 1948-1957 (Box 56b, Folder 21)
    - National Convention, 1960-1967 (Box 56b, Folder 22)
    - National Lawyers Guild v. Herbert Brownell, 1955 (Box 56b, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1936-1962 (Box 56b, Folder 24)
    - Nuremburg Trials, 1966 (Box 56b, Folder 25)
    - Oregon Chapter, 1961-1963 (Box 56b, Folder 26)
    - Organizational Material, 1951-1963 (Box 56b, Folder 27)
    - Popper, Martin, 1943-1947 (Box 56b, Folder 28)
    - Position Papers, Undated, 1954-1968 (Box 56b, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases, 1947-1963 (Box 56c, Folder 1)
    - Program and Administration Committee, 1952-1963 (Box 56c, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Undated (Box 56c, Folder 3)
    - Resolutions, 1948-1962 (Box 56c, Folder 4)
    - Russell, Mary E., 1938-1939 (Box 56c, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Chapter, Undated, 1953 (Box 56c, Folder 6)
    - Sharp, Malcolm, 1956 (Box 56c, Folder 7)
    - Sheiner v. Florida, 1955 (Box 56c, Folder 8)
    - Silberstein, Robert, 1940-1956 (Box 56c, Folder 9)
    - Silverman, Arthur, 1949 (Box 56c, Folder 10)
    - Southern Conference Educational Fund, Inc., 1965 (Box 56c, Folder 11)
    - Statements, Undated, 1955-1965 (Box 56c, Folder 12)
    - Student Division, 1943-1949 (Box 56c, Folder 13)
    - Tax Returns, 1954-1962 (Box 56c, Folder 14)
    - Volunteers, Undated, 1948 (Box 56c, Folder 15)
    - Wittenberg, Philip, 1956 (Box 56c, Folder 16)
    - Women's Committee, 1954 (Box 56c, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series C: New York City Chapter Subject Files.
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Personal and Program, 1961 (Box 56c, Folder 18)
    - Banquet and Public Relations Committee, 1954 (Box 56c, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, 1951-1963 (Box 56c, Folder 20)
    - By-Laws, Undated, 1954 (Box 56c, Folder 21)
    - Committee of Finance and Membership, 1954-1957 (Box 56c, Folder 22)
    - Conference on Fiscal Problems of New York City, 1954 (Box 56c, Folder 23)
    - Convention Arrangements Committee, 1952 (Box 56c, Folder 24)
    - Committee on New York State Legislative Practices and Procedures, 1961 (Box 56c, Folder 25)
    - Defense of Demonstrators, Undated (Box 56c, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board, 1953-1962 (Box 56c, Folder 27)
    - Finance and Entertainment Committee, 1940-1955 (Box 56c, Folder 28)
    - Financial Statements, 1953-1955 (Box 56c, Folder 29)
    - Fundraisers, 1954-1961 (Box 56c, Folder 30)
    - Housing Conditions, 1953 (Box 56c, Folder 31)
    - Insurance, 1951 (Box 56c, Folder 32)
    - Membership, 1952-1961 (Box 56c, Folder 33)
    - New York City Council against Poverty, Undated (Box 56c, Folder 34)
    - New York Guild Lawyer, 1948-1955 (Box 56c, Folder 35)
    - New York Section of the 1962 Convention Committee, 1961 (Box 56c, Folder 36)
    - New York Section of the NationalCommittee on Constitutional Liberties, 1950-1953 (Box 56c, Folder 37)
    - Newsletter, 1962 (Box 56c, Folder 38)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1958-1967 (Box 56c, Folder 39)
    - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1948-1951 (Box 56c, Folder 40)
    - Organizational Materials, 1940-1967 (Box 56c, Folder 41)
    - Press Releases, 1947-1963 (Box 56c, Folder 42)
    - Referral Services, 1963 (Box 56c, Folder 43)
    - Schachter, Simon, 1950-1956 (Box 56c, Folder 44)
    - Serri, Frank, 1952-1956 (Box 56c, Folder 45)
    - Statements and Reports, 1946-1959 (Box 56c, Folder 46)
    - Tax Returns, 1945, 1946, 1952-1955 (Box 56c, Folder 47)
    - Teachers Union, 1953-1955 (Box 56c, Folder 48)
- Part 2, Series I: National Office Administrative and Organizational Records, 1931-2003
  - Subseries A: National Executive Board and National Executive Committee Minutes and Related Files.
    - Minutes: National Executive Board, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: National Executive Board, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: National Executive Board, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Minutes: National Executive Committee, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - National Executive Board, Undated, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - National Executive Board, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - National Executive Board, 1980-1984 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - National Executive Committee, Undated (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - National Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - National Executive Committee, Feb 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - National Executive Committee, Sep 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - National Executive Committee, Apr 1983-Aug 1983 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - National Executive Committee, Oct 1983-Nov 1983 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - National Executive Committee (Involving Designated Vice Presidents), 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - National Executive Committee (Involving Regional Vice Presidents), 1983-1986 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1984-Feb 1984 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - National Executive Committee, Oct 1984-Nov 1984 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - National Executive Committee, Feb 1985-Jun 1985 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - National Executive Committee, Jul 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1986 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - National Executive Committee, Feb 1986-May 1986 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - National Executive Committee, Jun 1986-Sep 1986 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - National Executive Committee, Oct 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1987-May-87 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - National Executive Committee, Jun 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1988-May 1988 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - National Executive Committee, Aug 1988 (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - National Executive Committee, Sep 1988-Nov 1988 (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - National Executive Committee, Dec 1988-Feb 1989 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - National Executive Committee, Mar 1989-Jun 1989 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - National Executive Committee, Jul 1989-Aug 1989 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - National Executive Committee, Oct 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1990-Jun 1990 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - National Executive Committee [I], Aug 1990-Nov 1990 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - National Executive Committee [II], Aug 1990-Nov 1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - National Executive Committee, Feb 1991-Apr 1991 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - National Executive Committee, Jul 1991-Aug 1991 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - National Executive Committee, Sep 1991-Nov 1991 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - National Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - National Executive Committee, Jan 1993-Apr 1993 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - National Executive Committee, May 1993-Nov 1993 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - National Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - National Executive Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: National Conventions.
    - National Conventions: General, Undated, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Austin, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Boston, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Santa Fe, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Chicago, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Atlanta, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Denver, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Denver (Accounting), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Denver (Skills Seminars), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Washington DC, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Washington DC (Convention Resolutions), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - St. Louis [I], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - St. Louis [II], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - St. Louis [III], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles (Workshop Planning), 1989 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Austin, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Austin (Planning Committee / NLG Austin), 1990 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Austin (Printed Materials), 1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Austin (Resolutions), 1990 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Seattle [I], 1991 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Seattle [II], 1991 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Seattle (Agenda Planning, Special Events), 1991 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Seattle (Brochure, Dinner, Journal, Exhibitors), 1991 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Seattle (Housing, Childcare), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Seattle (Resolutions), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Chicago 1992 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Chicago (Registration Materials), 1992 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Chicago (Resolutions), 1992 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Chicago (Convention Evaluations), 1992 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - New York 1993 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - New York (Initially Considered Locations: Philadelphia, Baltimore), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - New York (Finances), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - New York (Agenda - Correspondence, Notes, Masters), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - New York (Brochure, Publicity), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - New York ("Convention Packet" Materials), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - New York (Housing, Childcare), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - New York (Law Students), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - New York (Program Sites, Exhibitors), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - New York (Registration, Hospitality, Volunteers), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - New York (Resolutions & Voting), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - New York (Convention Evaluations), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Albuquerque, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Portland, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Washington DC, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Detroit, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Boston, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Tucson, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Pasadena, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Minneapolis, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: General Administrative and Organizational Files.
    - Banquet Journal Ads (1996) - Invoices & Checks, 1996-1997 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Bequests, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Billing: National Dues Billing System, 1982-1990 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Billing: Dues Return Reports - Monthly Summaries, 1983, 1990-1992 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing Reports, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing and Inactivation, Jan 1989-Jun 1989 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Billing: Resolicitation Billing and Reports, Aug 1989 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Billing: Dues Billing and Reports, Oct 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing and Inactivation/Purging, Jan 1990 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing and Inactivation, Apr 1990-May 1990 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Billing: Pre-Inactivation Billing, May 1990 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Billing: Dues Return Reports, May 1990 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing and Billing Reports, Jun 1990-Jul 1990 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing and Billing Report, Oct 1990 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Billing: Renewal Billing and Inactivation, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Billing: Reports, Mar 1992 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Billing: Reports, Apr 1992 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Budgets, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Budgets, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Budgets, 1996-1998 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Budgets and Financial Statements, 1988-1990 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Chapter Communications: DC, 1983-1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Chapter Communications: NYC, 1984-1991 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Chapter Communications: St. Louis, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Chapter Communications: Various, 1979-1991 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Dues Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Evaluations, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Chapter Leadership Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Chapter Memos: National Office Updates, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Chapter Memos: National Office Updates, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Chapter Memos: National Office Updates, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Chapter Organizing, 1990-1998 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Chapter Organizing - Dues System and Financial Responsibilities, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Chapter Organizing - Monographs (Including Drafts and Correspondence), 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Chapters: In Formation or Potential, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Chapters: Inactive or "Defunct", [1983]-1990 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Chapters: Jailhouse Inactive or "Defunct", 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Chapters (Student): Florida State University Controversy, 1990-1992 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Chapters (Student): Membership / Organizing, 1991-1992 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Columbia University NLG Chapter: Energy Project Funding Request, 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Committee Complaints, 1987-1990 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Committee Contacts Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Committees: Membership, 1988-1991 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Committees: Membership (Information Packets), 1990 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Committees: Membership (Member Responses), 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Committees: National Finance, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Committees: National Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Committees: Resolutions, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Constitution and Bylaws of the National Lawyers Guild, 1960-2001 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Contact Lists (NEC, LSIA, Committees, Chapters), 1988-1992 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Continuing Legal Education (CLE), 1990, Undated (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Cowan, Michael, 1987-1988 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Dudley, Barbara, 1983-1987 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Various, 1970-1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)